Guide to the Deutscher Schriftsteller-Verband. Mitteilungen, 1963-1989
Department of Special Collections
Mitteilungen,
1963-1989
M0712
Deutscher Schriftsteller-Verband.
1 linear ft. (85 v.)
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
The collection contains issues of Mitteilungen, an East German magazine, from 1963-1989. The collection also contains various posters associated with issues of the magazine.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1994.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
. 0$aGerman literature--Germany (East)
Collection Contents
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for July/August and November/December 1963. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen".[1964] (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-March and November 1965. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for June-December 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-April 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for May-November 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for June-December 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for March-April and June 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issue for December-November 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for March and June 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for October-December 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-May1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for June-October 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for October/November and December 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for January-July 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for August-December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen".[1985] (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen".[1986] (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen".[1987; except March-June] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for March-July 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". Issues for August-December 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Deutscher Schriftstellerverband der DDR: "Mitteilungen". [1989; Except October] (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Posters for East German Movies (DEFA); Progress Film Vertrieb VEB.[1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Posters for East German Movies (DEFA); Progress Film Vertrieb VEB.[1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Posters for Movies out of the Soviet-Union; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Posters for Movies out of the Soviet-Union; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Posters for West German Movies and West German Coproductions; Posters for Swedish Movies. Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Posters for Polish, Hungarian and Romanian Movies; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Posters for Czechoslovakian Movies; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Posters for Movies out of the USA; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Posters for French Movies; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Posters for French-Italian Coproductions; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Posters for Movies out of Italy, Spain, Denmark and Japan; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Posters for Movies out of England, and various Coproductions; Progress Film Vertrieb VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3, Folder 12)